Yeah, so let's start with the shadows of the features starting with the ear
Okay, I'm gonna go with some alizarin and somber. It's darker shapes
There yeah
More burnt umber in there the violets make it even darker. Okay. I can come down a bit
Okay inside of the ear a bit more on the red side red burnt umber and a bit more
Darker than that
Then around the edge of the ear a bit more red in there and up against the shadow
Just pure red up against that shadow in that shadow back
Okay, it's a little bit of shadow here and in there
Then around the low
It's a bit cooler a bit of green
To that shape here. You know a green that shape there. It's that steve
Here this underside
shadowy shape here. It's quite warm
in there
I might just group that with the
Shadow of the neck almost the same color. I'll adjust that afterwards. That was the
Burnt umber
Purple just gonna close that gap and always bring it back and down the back of the net there
Maybe a bit more
Burnt umber
Something similar to the hair
It's like a burnt umber green. Okay, burnt umber yellow burnt umber yellow. Now we can start to look at the
Virtual features
So just looking into the
My shape
Just gonna take some red right in there. Go with some straight red. I've got the lid and the underside of the lid
And I'm gonna say it's like a red
Same midviolet can put the
underside of the lid
in later
Iris we go for
Bits of dark violet
Some green
run off with a bit darker
Okay, put that in for the other side
That um
Touch of violet in there
Then a bit more red
Okay, let's stop playing the lid there and let's say some orange one of the eye the corner there there
Give me that
Eye shape and look at the nose
Okay, current of the nostril. Okay shadow of the nostril
Go with some
alizarin
Burnt umber more on the alizarin side
Then you go a bit more burnt umber
It's a bit warmer
Nostril
It's a bit more on the red side
Touch of
Made alizarin purple
In there
Red
Angel on the top
In the V
Above the nose
Now we're going to look at the
The lips
Just push this
So for that edge there a bit
Alizarin shape
Under the nose
Okay, then looking at the lips
So that's almost the same
Go with some
This shadow is going to go with some alizarin
Burnt umber
I'm going to need the lip
Just a bit more on the burnt umber side
Just a bit more browner
And in the lip
More orange
Change of plane
It's a bit lighter
It's on
More orange in there
Now we're going to look at this shape here
So to me
So I've got some
Violet
I'd say violet
Maybe like some in violet
Some orange
In there
In there to start off with
In
A bit more orange
In there
Around here
It's a bit darker
Just more violet
A bit darker
Purple
Orange
Change there
So that's roughly
Okay
Brown
Here's some purple
It's a bit cooler
With some yellow
Green
Take that brown down
Let's test that
A bit too dark
Need
Violet into that
Something around that
Tone
Okay
Then
Put the shadow
Shape of the shadow
Along that edge
Same tone
Then
Just going to mix up some
Bit of that background
That was the
Purple green
Just going to shape that eye
Darker
Just testing off to one side
Okay and just fixing that angle
Okay
So that is
Shadows of the features
Just made that iris a bit bigger
Like it's slightly wider
Purple green
Did that brown a bit higher
Sorry, on the side of the fillet
Okay
So that's the
So we can call that the features
Finished
Okay